uspromocodes.com 2010-05-26

# Privacy Policy - USPromoCodes.com

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy has been developed by **USPromoCodes.com** in order to notify our customers of our policies and demonstrate to you our serious commitment to privacy. Every time you visit or use this website, you acknowledge and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. **USPromoCodes.com** takes user privacy seriously and takes appropriate measures to protect your privacy. For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes only the domain name of the consumer, but not the e-mail address.

No one under 13, please! No part of this website is designed to appeal to children, and no one under 13 years old must disclose personal information on this site.

Learn more about protecting children's privacy online by visiting www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy.

Please be aware, that when you click on a link such as "Click To Show Coupon Code" or "Redeem Coupon" you will be directed to the website of the advertiser.

We inform you that we do collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, as well as aggregate information about what pages consumers frequent, plus user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information obtained is later used to improve the content of our Web page, to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, and to contact consumers for marketing purposes. We guarantee that this personal information is never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

**We do not set any cookies.**

To provide you with the most recent information that may be of interest to you, we have established business relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server of those companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

From time to time we may need to use customer information for some new, unanticipated uses not previously mentioned in our privacy notice. We claim that in case our information practices change at some time in the future we will let you know of these changes by posting the policy changes to our Web site so that you could opt out of these new uses. If you have concerns about how your information is used, check back at our Web site regularly.

**Changes to the Policy**

We reserve the right to update this privacy policy. If there are any material changes, we will either contact with you via e-mail or post notification prominently on our Web site prior the implementation of the changes takes place.

All registered trademarks are the property of their respective retailers.

Provided to you for your convenience and solely for informational purposes, **USPromoCodes.com** assumes no liability whatsoever for the use or interpretation of any information you obtain on this website. The website and its content are provided "as is," without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied.

**USPromoCodes.com** does its best to provide accurate and timely information on this website. **USPromoCodes.com** assumes no responsibility in connection with this information. **USPromoCodes.com** reserves the right to change or delete any services or products offered without notice. IN NO EVENT SHALL apromocode.com BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, including financial losses or damages that result from using any information provided on this website.

Occasionally, **USPromoCodes.com** may post on its website statements made by third parties. **USPromoCodes.com** may monitor such third party statements for accuracy, legality, ownership, or other characteristics, but is not obligated to do so. **USPromoCodes.com** expressly disclaims any and all liability for such third party statements.

**No Endorsement of Third-Party Links**

All product and brand names which are displayed on this website are trademarks of their respective owners. Any mention of such names on this website is solely for information purposes and in no case must be considered as an endorsement or a recommendation by **USPromoCodes.com** or its personnel.

Our website also provides many links to other resources on the Internet. We provide these links for your convenience only and in order to help you locate the resources that may be of interest to you.

**Policies and Terms Are Subject to Change without Notice**

We strive to let our users know of any changes in our policies, legal notices, and disclaimers. However, so that we could quickly and efficiently update, improve, and manage this website, we reserve the right to make such changes at any time, at our sole discretion, without notice.

**Please Note**

Before participating in any offer or promotion, please read the fine print associated with it. Check for yourself whether any merchant you are going to deal with is legitimate and reputable.
